What do you mean What happened wrong with us there
В смысле А что у нас там случилось не
Well you have an illegal
так Ну у вас незаконный государственный
coup d'etat We
переворот никакого у нас
didn't have any coup d'etat You
государственного переворота не было вы
made something up Yeah and Yanukovych Where
что-то придумали Ага а Янукович Куда
did he go Well he eliminated himself No
делся Ну он само устранил его не
one can overthrow him Good afternoon Hello I am from
никто добрый день Здравствуйте я из
Ukraine, the city of Khmelnitsky A  where are you from I am
Украины город Хмельницкий А вы откуда Я
from Moscow ROSI from Moscow itself or the
из Москвы РОСИ с самой Москвы или
region from Moscow itself understood understood
области с самой Москвы понял Понял
special operation support in the West
спецоперацию Поддержи западе жи
what again will you support special operation Well
что ещё раз спецоперацию
yes in the interests of
поддержите Ну да в интересах считаю
our citizens I consider Yeah And what are the interests here for
наших граждан Угу А в чём интересы вот
me I collect opinions like this
мне я вот так коллекционирую мнение в
what are the interests of yours yours You  are you a citizen of
чём интересы ваш ваши Вы же гражданин
Russia what are your interests Well there are
России в чём ваши интересы Ну есть
economic interests there are security
экономические интерес есть безопасности
interests all of which you think are
интерес ва все которые вот вы считаете
the reason why you attacked and Well let's go In
из-за чего вы напали и по Ну давайте В
general terms security interests
общих чертах интересы безопасности
are that too much
заключаются в том что слишком сильно
militarism Ukraine Yeah That's too
милитаризм Украину Угу Вот и слишком
much too much  Ukraine has a number of
сильно слишком большое количество
unresolved territorial claims,
территориальных претензий нерешённых
but Ukraine does not want to
есть у Украины Вот но Украина не хочет
resolve them, well, according to the law, yes, that is,
их решать э ну по закону да то есть если
if I wanted to, I would finish. If I wanted to, then the
бы хотела я закончу Если бы хотела то
issue, for example, about Crimea, I would resolve it.  Well, by
вопрос например по Крыму Решала бы ну
legal means Who among us, by
законным путём Кто у нас по праву
international law, can resolve
международному может решать
territorial disputes The Supreme Court is
территориальные споры Верховный суд у он
right
правильно
Here But unfortunately this did not happen Yes, there
Вот Но к сожалению этого не произошло Да
were no applications because there is a precedent
не было заявок поскольку есть прецедент
in the
да в
form of former Yugoslavia, so to speak, well
виде Югославии бывшей так скажем вот ну
and economically of course there are large
и экономически конечно там есть большие
deposits of capital there  and not only ours,
залежи капитала вот и не только нашего
for example, Chinese capital Yes, in the
там например китайского капитала Да в
form of Motorsich, bought out and then
виде моторсич выкуплен а потом
transferred to the state, just in the moment
переданного государст просто в моменте
Well, there are many In general, different
Ну есть много В общем разных
questions economically, you want to seize
вопро экономически вы хотите захватить
some resources in Ukraine Yes, no, you
какие-то ресурсы в Украине Да нет
misunderstand And what is the
неправильно понимаете А в чём
economic one again then well there  there is
экономический ещё раз тогда ну там есть
our capital
наш капитал
invested a large amount which is under
вложенный большое количество который под
threat
угрозой
yours this is whose Well the state of course On
ваш это чей Ну государство конечно На
which for example
какой например
Well for example
Ну например
Well for example here is the same
Ну например вот тот же
What motorsich What relation does your
Что моторсич Какое отношение ваше
state have to
государство имеет к
motorsich And didn't part of motorsich
моторсич А разве часть моторсич не
belong to belonged to the Russian Federation And who
принадлежала принадлежало РФ А кому
did it belong to Tell me so that I have more of
принадлежало Скажите чтобы я больше
these  mistakes are not done well the state of the Russian Federation
таких ошибок не дела ну государство РФ
is the shareholder of
разве есть акционерами
Morsi Well I ask you No
морси Ну вот я у вас спрашиваю Нет это
you just came up with the fact that the state of the Russian Federation
вы придумали только что государство РФ
is the shareholder of Morsi and who bought China
есть акционера морси а кто Китай купил
yes once the state the state is not the
да е раз государство государство не есть
shareholder of Motor Sici  further You
акционером мотор сичи дальше Вот вы
said that there is the capital of your
сказали что там капитал вашего
state, for example, where is it, I'm
государства где например вот мне
interested Listen, to be honest I don't
интересно Слушайте вот по правде не
remember, I need to clarify, yes, let's do it.
помню надо уточнить да то давайте Вот
Probably If you don't remember something, then it
наверное Если вы что-то не помните то
's better not to say such a thing, now regarding
лучше такое не утверждать вот тепер по
territorial disputes, do I
территориальным спорам я правильно
understand correctly that you seized  Crimea and you say
понимаю что вы захватили Крым и говорите
that you decide something through the UN court yes
что решайте через суд ООН что-то да
No I didn't say that I'm saying that you
Нет я такого не говорил Я говорю что вы
don't decide as you should decide but
не решаете так как должны решать по ещё
once again look again according to the law this is our
раз ещё раз смотри по закону это наша
territory Here it is internationally recognized
территория Вот международно признанная
you seized it illegally And what-  then
вы её захватили не по закону И что-то
now you say that
сейчас говорите что надо ж как-то было
we had to do something according to the law somehow, but explain to me
сделать нам по закону а Ну объясните мне
Whose law You said that it was according to the law
Каму закону Вы же сказали что по закону
No, you say that they seized it illegally
было Нет вы говорите что захватили не по
What law was violated You violated the
закону Какой закон нарушен вы нарушили
UN statute Yes, the sovereignty of our
статут ООН Да суверенитет нашего
state is
государства иши
where, where, where  this is in Crimea Yes in
где где где это в Крыму Да в
Crimea So what exactly Which one Name it
Крыму Так и что конкретно Какою Назовите
hundred and super look and we had for
ста и супер смотрите и у нас было
example the Treaty of Friendship and
например Договор о дружбе и
Cooperation between Russia and Ukraine
сотрудничества между Россией и Украиной
in 1997 So it was approved where it was clearly
в 97 году Так утверждён где Чётко
stated that we recognize the borders  each
сказано что мы признаём границы друг
other If you captured Crimea you no longer
друга Если вы захватили Крым вы уже не
recognize our borders
признаёте наши границы
so Who recognized this where is
так Кто такое признал где
the proof again look your
доказательство ещё раз смотрите ваши
troops are now your power is in
войска сейчас есть ваша власть есть в
Crimea of ​​course Crimea is a subject of the
Крыму конечно Крым - это субъект
Russian Federation how did it become a
Российской Федерации как он стал
subject of the Russian Federation if it is
субъектом Российской Федерации если это
part of
часть
Ukraine EU secession about  Well, it's a part That
Украины ЕС сецессия про Ну это часть То
is, you took away a part of another
есть вы забрали се часть другого
state No, you know what the word secession is, I'm
государства Нет вы слово сецессия знаете
saying it again, you got in,
что не ещё раз говорю вы забрались
look, let's do it this way, Crimea was a
смотрите давайте так э Крым - это была
part of Ukraine, it was a part Yes, Ukraine
часть Украины была часть Да была Украина
was taken into Russia No,
брали её в состав России Нет ещё раз
secession happened again  explain
сецессия произошла ещё раз объясни
Explain Explain the process itself how part of
Объясни Объясните сам процесс как часть
Ukraine ended up in part of Russia I was the
Украины оказалась в части России Я
first to ask the question the word sitse I don't know
первый задал вопрос слово сице я не знаю
Look I don't know the word I don't give me I don't
Смотри я не знаю слово я не давайте я не
know the word sitse explain to me the process
знаю слова сице объясните мне процесс
explain to me the process how it happened
объясните мне процесс как так получилось
that there was a state called Ukraine
что вот было государство Украина
ninety-first  year it was created and
девяносто первый год оно создалось и
your state In ninety-first year
ваше государство В девяносто первом году
two independent states were created
создалось вот два независимых
like this In ninety-seventh year
государства так В девяносто седьмом году
we signed a treaty of friendship and
у нас был подписан договор о дружбе и
cooperation like this where it was clearly
сотрудничестве так вот где чётко было
stated that we recognize each
сказано что мы признаём границы друг
other's borders and so on How so  it turned out
друга и так дальше Да как так сталось
that now you do not recognize our borders
что теперь Вы не признаёте наши границы
that you recognized in 1997 Let's
которые вы признавали в 97 году Давайте
explain again now it
можете объяснить ещё раз сейчас
is called manipulation on your part no
называется манипуляция с вашей стороны
one denies Yes what about Ukraine
никто не не отрицает Да что Украины
Ukraine is a separate state with
Украина там отдельное государство со
its own borders so secession happened
своими границами так произошла сецессия
you changed power illegally
у вас поменялась власть незаконным путём
108 109  110 111 articles what articles and
108 109 110 111 статьи чего статьи и
Crimea did not agree with this what articles of
Крым с этим был не согласен чего статьи
your Constitution were in effect at that time I
вашей Конституции на тот момент действу
mean And what happened there
В смысле А что у нас там случилось не
wrong Well you have an illegal coup d'etat
так Ну у вас незаконный государственный
nobody We
переворот никого У нас государственного
did not have a coup d'etat you came up with something
переворота не было вы что-то придумали
Yeah and  by what law was the
Ага а по ка по какому закону свергли
president overthrown? We haven't
президента ещ у нас не
overthrown him yet or what? And Yanukovych? Where did
свергать или что а Янукович Куда делся
he go? Well, he's self-eliminating. And
Ну он самоустранение
how was he overthrown?
а как его свергли ну
Well, tell me or. Well, what happened to
скажите или Ну что случилось с
him? Well, tell me.
ним ну расскажите мне вот интересно вот
I'm interested. I like it when some particularly smart
я люблю когда какие-то особенно умные
Russians tell stories.  us about some kind of
русские Да рассказывают нам про какой-то
state I was just here at
государственный род Я просто тут был в
that time tell me what happened to
это время расскажите мне что случилось с
Yanukovych here's how he was
Януковичем вот как его
overthrown I'll explain was at  you president
свергли объясняю был у вас президент
Yanukovych then you had Euromaidan
Янукович затем у вас произо Евромайдан
so then with Ozi Madan an agreement was concluded
так итем с Ози мадана был заключен
and this agreement was not fulfilled
и и договор этот не выполнялся
and that's it
и
and you overthrew the president then the
И всё И свергли вы президент затем
Verkhovna Rada I explain I explain How
Верховная Рада объясняю объясняю Как
then the Verkhovna Rada of Ukraine issued the decree of the
затем Верховная Рада Украины выдала указ
Verkhovna Rada 757 dash series not a decree
Верховной Рады 757 дефис се римс не указ
resolution resolution on decree not
а постанова постановление о на указа не
decree of the president we have so and so so the
указ президента у нас так Так и что так
Verkhovna Rada had no right what what kind of
Верховная Рада не имела права что что за
resolution again what kind of
постановление ещё раз что за
resolution
постановление
e once again what did the Verkhovna Rada adopt a decree on
е раз что приняла Верховная Рада указ о
self-elimination once again what What is the essence of
самоустранение ещ раз что В чём суть
it What is the essence You will say  that they overthrew well
его В чём суть Вы скажете что свергли ну
there is a resolution there that she overthrew
есть там постановление что она свергать
him like
его типа
she that there is a fact recorded there that he
она что там зафиксирован факт что он
eliminated himself there is a fact recorded there that
устранил там зафиксирован тот факт что
Yanukovych is no longer
Янукович больше не
president you can read the text of this
президент можете прочитать текст этого
decree the text of the resolution
указа текст постановы
now on
сейчас на
Yes I love such experts on our
Да люблю таких экспертов по нашей
Constitution Yeah
Конституции Угу
so the resolution of the Verkhovna Rada  Ukraine
так постановление Верховной Рады Украины
on the self-removal of the President of Ukraine from the
о самоустранение президента Украины от
exercise of constitutional powers of
выполнения конституционных полномочий
appointment outside the regular elections of the
назначения вне очередных выборов
President of Ukraine, given that the
президента Украины учитывая что
President  Ukraine Yanukovych himself removed
президент Украины Янукович само устранил
from the exercise of constitutional powers,
от выполнения конституционных полномочий
which threatens the governability of the state,
что угрожает управляемости государство
territorial integrity and
территориальной целостности и
sovereignty of Ukraine, mass violation of the
суверенитету Украины массовому нарушению
rights and freedoms of citizens, based on
прав и свобод граждан исходя из
the circumstances of the region, the necessity of
обстоятельств краи необходимости
expressing the sovereign will of the Ukrainian
выражают суверенную волю украинского
people, the Verkhovna Rada of Ukraine
народа Верховной рад Украины
decides to establish that the President of
постановляет установить что президент
Ukraine
Украины
Yakovych constitutionally
якови конституционным способом
removed the first point in accordance with point
устранил первый пункт согласно пункту
seven  parts one of article eighty-
седьмой части первой статьи восемьдесят
fifth and so on there are three points the
пятой Ну и так далее там три пункта
present resolution comes into force
настоящие постановление вступает в силу
from the moment of its adoption Yes Read where it
с момент его принятия Да Прочитайте где
is written that the Verkhovna Rada
написано что Верховная Рада
has withdrawn Article 8 of the Constitution
отстранилась 8я статья Конституции
has been violated once again once again he
нарушена ещё раз ещё раз он постанова
does not sign the resolution of the Verkhovna Rada we have
Верховной рада не подписывает у нас
again the Verkhovna Rada does not sign
поснова Верховной Рады не подписывает
President, you said again that she eliminated him,
президент ещё раз вы сказали что она его
what is written in the Verkhovna Rada that he
что написано в Верховной Раде что он
eliminated himself, therefore he cannot,
само устранил поэтому он не может ещ раз
look again Wait, what do you mean he cannot, you
смотри Подожди Что значит не может ты
said that he was eliminated, you can find
сказал что его устранили Ты можешь найти
where
где
he was eliminated, read again,
его где устранили Прочитай ещё раз
read the word
прочитай слово
eliminate Well, well  it is written that the
устраняем Ну ну написано само устранил
Supreme One eliminated it  The Rada did not eliminate it
вот Верховная Рада не устраняла она
const
конста
pre Verkhovna Rada Verkhovna Rada
пре Верховная Рада Верховная Рада
violated again Listen look what she
нарушила ещё раз Послушай смотри что она
did the second point did not violate the law of
сделала вторым пунктом не нарушила зако
Ukraine verkhov ra 108 article of the
Украины верхов ра 108 стаю
Constitution
Конституции
con Yes Shut up 108 article of the contu of
кон Да Помолчите 108 статья конту
Ukraine in front of my face the president of
Украины у меня перед лицом президент
Ukraine exercises his powers until the
Украины исполняет свои полномочия до
entry into office of the elected  the
вступления на постного избранного
president of Ukraine the powers of the president of
президента Украины полномочия президента
Ukraine are terminated early in the event of
Украины прекращаются досрочно в случае
resignation inability to exercise his
отставки невозможности исполнять свои
powers removal from office by way of
полномочия смещения с поста в порядке
impeachment sm so everything so none
импичмента сме так всё так ни к одному
of these
из этих
resolution resolution where it is
постановление постановление где Сказано
said where it is said that Yanukovych ceases to be
где Сказано что Янукович перестаёт быть
president No
президентом Нет ещё раз
look again the resolution of the Verkhovna Rada
смотрите постанова Верховной Рады
says that Yanukovych  self-elimination
говорит что Янукович самоустранение
Well, look at the second point E once
Ну посмотрите вот второй пункт Е раз ещё
again the second point Look at this
раз второй пункт Посмотрите этой
resolution You yourself
постановы Вы же сами его
read it at the Technical University
зачитывались в Техническом университете
super very good so we as a lawyer and a
супер очень хорошо вот мы как юрист и
Technical specialist will talk to you
Технический специалист поговорим с вами
now about the constitution it is interesting
сейчас вот про конституцию онь интересно
look you read somewhere there about  I
смотрите вы где-то там вычитали про
will decree Yes, but you read it and you didn’t
постанову Да но вы её зачитали и вы не
find it  that the Verkhovna Rada is eliminating the
нашли что Верховная Рада устраняет
Verkhovna Rada states the fact that
Верховная Рада констатирует факт что
President Yanukovych has eliminated himself, therefore
президент Янукович само устранил поэтому
it appoints elections for a date like
она назначает выборы на э число типа
In 3 months What will there be elections if
Через 3 месяца Да что будут выборы если
Yanukovych is not eliminating himself
Янукович не самоустранение
Where is it said that he ceases to be
где Сказано что он перестаёт быть
president in this decree it is not said in a
президентом в этом указе сказано не
decree but in a resolution these are different things  the
указе а постановление это разные дру
president's self-removal from exercising
самоустранение президента от выполнения
constitutional powers what does
конституционных полномочий что это
this mean this means that the Verkhovna
означает это Это означает что Верховная
Rada states that he is self-removal
рада констатирует что он самоустранение
look the Verkhovna Rada has violated this law
смотри Верховная рада это зако нарушила
what What is the Supreme Council according to the
что Что такое Верховный Совет по
Constitution The Verkhovna Rada can well the
Конституции Верховная Рада может ну
Supreme Council in your opinion yes it will be Hi
Верховный Совет по-вашему да будет Хай
will be no Verkhovna Rada so it will be  what
будет нет Верховная Рада так будет что
is Parla Tae
такое Парла Тае
parliament what is its
парламент в чём его
function Well probably in
функция Ну наверное в государстве в
each state it is different I don't know about each it is
каждом по-разному Я не знаю ка каждом
different yes that is Legislative
по-разному да то есть Законодательная
power so look You know about the
власть так смотрите Вы знаете про
division of power into three branches
разделение власти на три ветви
legislator of
законодатель
destinies
судеб
so the Supreme Council is also a branch of
так Верховный Совет это тоже ветка
power  yes that is if you Now the second
власти да то есть если вы Теперь второе
Open the Constitution So tell
Откройте Конституцию Так и скажите
me tell me what body determines
мне скажите мне какой орган определяет
the legality or illegality of this or
Законность или незаконность того или
that  normative legal
иного нормативно-правового
act
акта
[music]
[музыка]
constitution decree or law or the
конституция постановление или закон или
president issued a decree So who decides which body
президент издал указ Так кто какой орган
whether this decree or
решает соответствует ли этот указ или
decree complies with the Constitution Well, well, the court
постановление Конституции А ну ну суд
probably
наверное
what Well, I don’t know what they are like that No,
какой Ну я не знаю какой они так вот Не
no, look, you are such
нет смотри вы же такой
constitutionalists Well,  look Yes
конституционалисты а Ну посмотрите Да у
I have the Law before my eyes and the
меня перед глазами Закон и рядом
Constitution nearby yes Tell me
Конституция да Скажите
look Read here
смотрите Прочитайте вот
Take Take the section constitutional
Возьмите Возьмите раздел конституционный
court
суд
let's take the section in the
давайте что ещё раз взять раздел в
Constitution again Look at the constitutional
Конституции Посмотрите конституционный
court Well, let's get you
суд А ну давайте сейчас мы вас получим
a little bit now So what article what
немножко Так какая стать что какая
article section Look at the control F
статья раздел Посмотрите контро F
press  constitutional court
нажмите конституционный суд
so
так двенадцатый
section twelfth And what should I do next so
раздел И что мне дальше делать так
Read here article 147 Yes 147
Прочитайте вот статью 147 Да 147
Yes the constitutional court of Ukraine decides
Да конституционный суд Украины решает
issues of conformity with the Constitution of Ukraine
вопросы соответствия Конституции Украины
of laws of Ukraine provided for by the
законов Украины предусмотренных
Constitution of other acts
Конституции случая других актов
carry out official interpretation of
осуществляют официальное толкование
the Constitution of Ukraine as well as other
Конституции Украины а также иные
powers in accordance with the present
полномочия соответствии с настоя
ntu is based on the principles of the Supreme
нту основывается на принципах Верховного
Independence
Независимости
collegially Which body
коллегиально Какой орган
determines whether it complies with the law
определяет соответствует закону
of the Constitution Yes, they
Конституции Да
bombed another one,
всё разбомбили ещё одного
so illegally Yanukovych, everything, like there
тако незаконно Янукович всё да типа там
Oh, I have a technical education
О я там техническое образование
there, damn, damn, somehow with him, even just like
там блин блин как-то с ним даже дуже
that  So you start, you have an
просто так Даки еши начинают у вас там
illegal constitutional court there, in short, you
конституционный суд незаконный короче
have to unwind it even more. And here there
там приходится довше разматывать А тут
is a guy, so look, it’s not
есть чувак так вот смотрите все не вот
this Vanka. In short, neither I nor anyone from the
этот Ванька Короче ни я ни какой-то с
street determines the legality or not, well,
улицы не определяет Законность или не ну
in accordance or non-compliance with
в соответствие или несоответствие
the Constitution of this or that
Конституции того или иного
norm.  -legal act if uh
нормативно-правового акта если ээ
some uh like this yes thinks that this
какой-то э вот такой да считает что это
resolution does not comply with the
постановление не соответствует
Constitution Yes there is uh an appeal to the
Конституции Да есть ээ обращение в
Constitutional Court Yes that uh from someone
Конституционный суд Да тот э от кого-то
who is the subject of the constitutional
Кто есть субъектом конституционного пода
submission Yes and the constitutional court makes
подани Да и конституционный суд выносит
its verdict Yes does it comply or not
своё вердикт Да соответствует или не
it corresponds to this Constitution, so that
соответствует этой Конституции так то
is, for these 9 years, no one, no one filed,
есть за эти 9 лет никто никто не подал
neither Yanukovych nor the deputies, no
ни тот Янукович да тогда ни депутаты
one filed, so that the Supreme
никто не подал да о том чтоб Верховный
Court would recognize this as not
суд признал это тому что не
corresponding to the Constitution, therefore, as they
соответствует Конституции поэтому они
all say, the Verkhovna
как все говорят там Верховная
Rada overthrew the president, removed
Рада там свергла президента отстранил
him  didn't step aside,
его не отстранилась
elections are scheduled. In 3 months, yes, that
назначают выборы Через 3 месяца да то
is, if he had
есть если бы он
returned, everything would have been fine, but
вернулся всё было бы нормально но так
since he eliminated himself, the election process is underway in 3 months,
как он само устранил Через 3 месяца идёт
yes, that is, what is the
избирательный процесс да то есть в чём
problem?  And
проблема И
when these constitutionalists who
когда вот эти конституционалисты которые
opened some one article there They
открыли там какую-то одну статью Они
don't understand anything at all Yes, but when
вообще не понимают ничего Да но когда и
you get to at least the Constitutional
доходишь хотя бы до Конституционного
Court, it explodes and he
суда у него вот взрывается и он
switches, so put all the likes,
переключается поэтому поставьте все лайк
all
все
of them, knowing the Constitution of Ukraine Yes, from
е одного знав Конституции Украины Да из
Moscow, so pi  binding on the channel so that's
Москвы так пи обовязково на канал так
it, just whoever got the
воно того варту просто хто отримав
aesthetics and moral satisfaction I just
эстетичны и мораль задоволення Я просто
got it I'm enjoying it When you know this moment
отримав я кайфую Коли знаете оцей момент
When I'm starting to remember that
Коли вони начинаю начинать пом така
inside In short, like the squeak and
внутр вних Короче джит так лайк писка и
tell your friends about the
розкажить друзям про
channel, write to your tel right now, o and
канал пись на й tel прям зараз о а
pok  this is very and very important YouTube is busy
пок це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube заня
with us through srg or in your ban and very
нас через срг ор в твый бан и дуже
many videos I do not show to people sometimes I do not
багато вдео не показую людям вчасно не
show information about streams so
показуе информация про стримы тому для
that we Mali promptly
того щоб ми Мали оперативный звязок
write links right now and while there in telegram
пишиться прямо зараз а пок там в телегра
okm
окм
video library and useful information and
видеотека и корисна информация и пон
understand the current operational links
тримати постийний оперативный звязок
independently in order to show you about this
незалежно в того чи покаже вам про це
YouTube Glory to Ukraine
YouTube Слава Украине
signature N
пидпись N